<resources>
  <string name="createNFC">Create NFC Tag</string>
  <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>
    <string name="toggle">Toggle</string>
    <string name="nullStr"></string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="gotIt">Got It!</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="nope">Nope</string>
    <string name="nevermind">Nevermind</string>
         <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
         <string name="close">Close</string>
        <string name="exitBtn">Exit</string>
        <string name="no">No!</string>
        <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="whatsnew">What\'s New</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    
    <string name="nfcToast">Performing NFC RelayRemote action&#8230;</string>
    <string name="aboutNFC">Cool! You have an NFC device!\n\nTo make an NFC tag, you first need a tag.
                            If you don\'t have one, order some and then come back here. If you have one
                            ready to go, read on.\n\nTo create an NFC tag, select an action on the next
                            menu to take for this relay; either always turn on, always turn off, or
                            toggle the current state. Then just touch your NFC tag to your device for
                            a second or two until you see a confirmation message. That\'s it!</string>
    
    <string-array name="nfcCmdOptions">
        <item>Turn On</item>
        <item>Turn Off</item>
        <item>Toggle</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="app_name">NFC Remote</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">NFC Remote</string>
  <string name="pref_user_name">Server address</string>
    <string name="pref_user_name_summary">Set Irdroid WIFI / LIRC server IP address</string>
    <string name="pref_user_profile">Server Settings</string>
   <string name="about_text">Irdroid NFC Remote is a LIRC (Linux infrared remote control) client that allows you to create custom infrared remote control sequences or macros. The app works with LIRC and Winlirc servers and it is specially designed to work with Irdroid WIFI modules.</string>
   <string name="about_code_copyright">Copyright 2013 Irdroid</string>
   <string name="about_url">Visit: http://www.irdroid.com</string>
   <string name="about_license">The application is open source, licensed under GNU GPL v2.0 . You are free to distribute, modify and use for commercial purposes</string>
    <string name="nfcNotSupportedErrorTitle">NFC Not Supported</string>
        <string name="nfcNotSupportedError">This device does not support NFC.</string>
        <string name="nfcDisabledErrorTitle">NFC Disabled</string>
        <string name="nfcDisabledError">This device supports NFC, but it is disabled. Enable it in the device\'s settings.</string>
        <string name="nfcReadOnlyErrorTitle">NFC Read Only</string>
        <string name="nfcReadOnlyError">The NFC tag is read only.</string>
        <string name="nfcFormattingErrorTitle">Formatting Error</string>
        <string name="nfcFormattingError">There was an error formatting the NFC tag.</string>
        <string name="nfcTagLostErrorTitle">Tag Lost</string>
        <string name="nfcTagLostError">The tag was lost or pulled away while writing to it.</string>
        <string name="nfcNoNdefErrorTitle">Invalid Tag</string>
        <string name="nfcNoNdefError">The NFC tag does not support NDEF format.</string>
        <string name="nfcBadSpaceErrorTitle">Not Enough Space</string>
        <string name="nfcBadSpaceError">The NFC tag cannot hold the amount of data required.</string>
        <string name="nfcUnknownErrorTitle">Unknown Error :(</string>
        <string name="nfcUnknownError">An unknown error occurred while writing to the NFC tag.</string> 
  <string name="nfcWrittenTitle">Success!</string>
    <string name="nfcWritten">The NFC tag was written successfully.</string>
   
   
      <string name="about_art_copyright">All artwork Copyright 2013 Irdroid</string>
     <string name="firstrun_text">This application requires a configured and working LIRC daemon (for Unix OS) or Winlirc (For Windows). The application is a LIRC client that is specially designed for Irdroid WIFI module (see the link below). If you want to use this app with Irdroid WIFI , click on the link below to purchase a WIFI module.</string>
       <string name="purchase_url">Purchase a unit: http://www.irdroid.com</string>
         <string name="app_usage">The application allows you to setup custom Infrared remote control sequences/macros, creation of macro shortcuts and writing macros to NFC Tags, from the app main screen tap on Add in order to add new Macro. Enter the name of your new macro and tap on SAVE. In order to add command sequences to your new macro long click on the newly created macro and select "Edit Macro" a new screen pops up and you can use the Add button to add custom commands to your newly created macro. To execute a macro just tap on the macro name. You can also write your macros to NFC tags and start the macros by tapping a TAG.</string>
      <string name="todo">TODO</string>
</resources>